♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 36=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 36 =
(President: Fu Sihan)
(الرئيس: فو سيهان)
It's time to change to another one.
حان الوقت للتغيير إلى واحد آخر.
Ms. Fu.
السيدة فو.
Do you think it's that easy
هل تعتقد أنه بهذه السهولة
to become the new president?
ليصبح الرئيس الجديد؟
Guards.
حراس.
Do you still remember Yang Shan, Ms. Fu?
هل ما زلت تتذكر يانغ شان ، السيدة فو؟
Anything I can do for you, Ms. Fu?
هل يمكنني فعل أي شيء من أجلك يا سيدة فو؟
It's fine now. You may go.
كل شيء على ما يرام الآن.  يمكنك الذهاب.
Yes, Ms. Fu.
نعم ، السيدة فو.
Ms. Fu, I suppose you already know
السيدة فو ، أعتقد أنك تعرف بالفعل
that Fu Sihan and I got back together.
أن فو سيهان وصلنا معًا.
He can't live without me.
لا يستطيع العيش بدوني.
I'm not running a relationship show.
أنا لا أدير برنامج علاقة.
My time is precious.
وقتي ثمين.
What do you want to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
Fu Sihan has always been suspecting
لطالما كان فو سيهان يشك
that the car crash wasn't an accident at all,
أن حادث السيارة لم يكن حادثًا على الإطلاق ،
but a plot.
لكن مؤامرة.
He's been investigating for all these years.
لقد كان يحقق طوال هذه السنوات.
Not long ago,
منذ وقت ليس ببعيد،
he went to the US
ذهب إلى الولايات المتحدة
to see someone.
لرؤية شخص ما.
And that person
وهذا الشخص
is related to the car crash.
مرتبط بحادث السيارة.
I've heard that you used to make comics.
سمعت أنك اعتدت على عمل رسوم هزلية.
Don't you think this one is a bit cliche?
ألا تعتقد أن هذا هو مبتذل بعض الشيء؟
He is the former president's secretary, Yang Shan.
هو سكرتير الرئيس السابق ، يانغ شان.
Yang Shan told him that there was an event data recorder in the car,
أخبره يانغ شان أن هناك مسجل بيانات حدث في السيارة ،
which recorded everything that happened.
التي سجلت كل ما حدث.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Are you trying to say that he has the data records?
هل تحاول أن تقول أن لديه سجلات البيانات؟
It's a real pity.
إنه لأمر مؤسف حقيقي.
The recorder was already destroyed, as someone's will.
تم تدمير المسجل بالفعل ، حسب إرادة شخص ما.
But,
ولكن،
for his own safety,
من أجل سلامته الشخصية ،
he kept another copy.
احتفظ بنسخة أخرى.
And that copy
وتلك النسخة
is right here in my hand.
هنا في يدي.
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
I'll believe everything you say?
سوف أصدق كل ما تقوله؟
You know what, Ms. Fu?
هل تعلم ماذا يا سيدة فو؟
The car crash was caused by brake malfunction.
كان سبب تحطم السيارة هو عطل في الفرامل.
And someone
وشخص ما
had changed the braking line furtively.
غيرت خط الكبح بشكل خفي.
How much do you want?
كم تريد؟
Do you think you can get rid of me just with money?
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنك التخلص مني بالمال فقط؟
Now Fu Sihan has lost the company.
الآن خسر فو سيهان الشركة.
If I can't be the wife of the president,
إذا لم أستطع أن أكون زوجة الرئيس ،
I want to be the vice chairwoman of the group.
أريد أن أكون نائبة رئيس المجموعة.
How does that sound?
كيف يبدو هذا؟
Ms. Fu.
السيدة فو.
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
We are the same kind of people.
نحن من نفس النوع من الناس.
You have quite an ambition.
لديك طموح كبير.
Fu Rong! You...
فو رونغ! أنت ...
Want to blackmail me?
تريد ابتزازي؟
No way.
مستحيل.
Today you want to be the vice chairwoman.
اليوم تريد أن تكون نائبة الرئيس.
And tomorrow you would want my seat.
وغدا تريد مقعدي.
Fu Rong, are you even human?
فو رونغ ، هل أنت حتى بشر؟
How could you do that to your own brother?
كيف يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك بأخيك؟
He was not my real brother.
لم يكن أخي الحقيقي.
As long as he was alive,
طالما كان حيا ،
the group would never be mine.
لن تكون المجموعة لي أبدًا.
Even if it was really me who did it,
حتى لو كنت أنا من فعل ذلك حقًا ،
without any evidence,
بدون أي دليل ،
what can you do to me?
ماذا تستطيع ان تفعل بي
Dad!
أب!
Sihan! You...
سيهان! أنت ...
Dad.
أب.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Fu Rong.
فو رونغ.
How could you be so evil?
كيف يمكن أن تكون شريرا جدا؟
I raised you up
لقد ربيتك
as one of my own children.
كواحد من أطفالي.
How could you do such an abominable thing?
كيف يمكنك أن تفعل مثل هذا الشيء المقيت؟
I suggest that you turn yourself in.
أقترح أن تقوم بتسليم نفسك.
And take responsibility
وتحمل المسؤولية
for everything you've done.
لكل ما فعلته.
Do something decent for once in your life,
افعل شيئًا لائقًا لمرة واحدة في حياتك ،
since we've spent so many years together.
منذ أن أمضينا سنوات عديدة معًا.
I was an orphan.
كنت يتيما.
I have done everything you asked during the past 40 years.
لقد فعلت كل ما طلبته خلال الأربعين عامًا الماضية.
I was always more capable than my brother.
كنت دائمًا أكثر قدرة من أخي.
But you wanted to give him the company,
لكنك أردت أن تمنحه الشركة ،
just because I'm not your own blood.
فقط لأنني لست من دمك.
You treat Yun Xiangxiang better than me, even if you've only known her for days.
أنت تعامل Yun Xiangxiang أفضل مني ، حتى لو كنت تعرفها منذ أيام فقط.
I'm always an outsider in this family.
أنا دائمًا من الخارج في هذه العائلة.
Right?
حق؟
Old man?
رجل عجوز؟
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Why are you so stubborn?
لماذا أنت عنيد جدا؟
You disappoint me so much!
لقد خيبت ظني كثيرا!
You murdered your own kin
لقد قتلت أقاربك
just for a position.
فقط لمنصب.
You are frenzied!
أنت مجنون!
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
we are not father and daughter anymore.
لم نعد أبًا وابنة.
Henceforth,
من الآن فصاعدا ،
we have no relation whatsoever.
ليس لدينا علاقة على الإطلاق.
And you...
وأنت...
You are on your own.
أنت لوحدك.